<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Team on Impact17 | Partnering for a better world</title>
    <link>/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Team on Impact17 | Partnering for a better world</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2019-2020 [Impact17](https://impact17.net) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Andy Andrea</title>
      <link>/team/andy-andrea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/andy-andrea/</guid>
      <description>Chief Executive Officer Andy is Director of Alliance4Impact, Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Impact17, and Chair of the Board of the Sustainable Impact Association, all dedicated to supporting and building partnerships for social good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Dickie</title>
      <link>/team/david-dickie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/david-dickie/</guid>
      <description>BDD David spent his early career in financial roles in manufacturing and publishing before a number of commercial roles in the advertising industry. David is passionate about helping alleviate poverty with a commercial approach to humanitarian issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irina Bolgari</title>
      <link>/team/irina-bolgari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/irina-bolgari/</guid>
      <description>Head of Research Irina is Head of Research at Impact17 and Project Officer at Alliance4Impact. In both organizations, Irina promotes cross-sector partnerships on humanitarian action and the SDGs. In her current role, Irina oversees and conducts research projects to better understand multi-stakeholder partnerships from academic and practical perspectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lily Jones-Herbst</title>
      <link>/team/lily-jones-herbst/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/lily-jones-herbst/</guid>
      <description>Researcher Lily is working as a researcher for Impact17 and is based in the UK. Lily is currently conducting a research project aimed at building a better understanding of partnership perceptions, challenges and opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marta Zaragoza Navarro</title>
      <link>/team/marta-zaragoza/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/marta-zaragoza/</guid>
      <description>Researcher After having been based in Berkeley and Geneva, Marta is currently enrolled in a Dual Master’s Degree in International Public Management and International Relations jointly offered by Sciences Po Paris and Peking University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roshni Mahesh</title>
      <link>/team/roshni-mahesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/roshni-mahesh/</guid>
      <description>Researcher Roshni is volunteering as a Researcher for Impact 17. Having witnessed the inequalities that exist whilst growing up in India and East Africa, she is passionate about facilitating sustainable development that create level playing fields for individuals to tap into their potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Ganly</title>
      <link>/team/steve-ganly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/steve-ganly/</guid>
      <description>CTO Steve is better at writing code that writing bios&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Meredith</title>
      <link>/team/steve-meredith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/steve-meredith/</guid>
      <description>Creative Steve?s formative years were spent in the creative departments of several London advertising agencies, working as a Copywriter then Creative Director, producing campaigns for both local and global brands across different industry sectors, and picking up a few creative awards along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Delaney</title>
      <link>/team/sydney_delaney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/sydney_delaney/</guid>
      <description>Researcher Sydney is a researcher at Impact17. Her work in the organization revolves around intersectional partnerships between international organizations and the private sector, with the common interest of the SDGs. Her current projects focus primarily on research and relationship development with American companies looking to develop stronger partnerships within the international sector.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>